<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="citations.xsl"?>
<collection language="en">
	<quote author="Aristotle">A constitution is the arrangement of magistracies in a state</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">A friend to all is a friend to none</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">A great city is not to be confounded with a populous one</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">A true friend is one soul in two bodies</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">All men by nature desire knowledge</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">All paid jobs absorb and degrade the mind</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">All virtue is summed up in dealing justly</quote>
	<quote author="Aristotle">Courage is a mean with regard to fear and confidence</quote>
	<quote author="Woody Allen">Life doesn't imitate art, it imitates bad television</quote>
	<quote author="Isaac Asimov">Violence is the last refuge of the incompetent</quote>
	<quote author="J.S. Bell">No theory of reality compatible with quantum theory can require spatially separate events to be independent</quote>
	<quote author="Claude Bernard">Man can learn nothing except by going from the known to the unknown</quote>
	<quote author="Niels Bohr">Whoever talks about Planck's constant and does not feel at least a little giddy obviously doesn't appreciate what he is talking about</quote>
	<quote author="Niels Bohr">How wonderful that we have met with a paradox. Now we have some hope of making progress</quote>
	<quote author="Niels Bohr">The opposite of a fact is falsehood, but the opposite of one profound truth may very well be another profound truth</quote>
	<quote author="Niels Bohr">Your theory is crazy, but it's not crazy enough to be true</quote>
	<quote author="Niels Bohr">If quantum mechanics hasn't profoundly shocked you, you haven't understood it yet</quote>
	<quote author="Antoine Bourdelle">The secret of art is love</quote>
	<quote author="Giordano Bruno">It is proof of a base and low mind for one to wish to think with the masses or majority, merely because the majority is the majority. Truth does not change because it is, or is not, believed by a majority of the people</quote>
	<quote author="Buddha">Thousands of candles can be lighted from a single candle, and the life of the candle will not be shortened. Happiness never decreases by being shared</quote>
	<quote author="Buddha">Beings are owners of their action, heirs of their action</quote>
	<quote author="Lord Byron">The power of Thought, the magic of the Mind !</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Camus">Don't walk in front of me, I may not follow. Don't walk behind me, I may not lead. Just walk beside me and be my friend</quote>
	<quote author="Dale Carnegie">It isn't what you have, or who you are, or where you are, or what you are doing that makes you happy or unhappy. It is what you think about</quote>
	<quote author="Lewis Carroll">Sometimes I've believed as many as six impossible things before breakfast</quote>
	<quote author="Lewis Carroll">Curiouser and curiouser !</quote>
	<quote author="Castaneda">We choose only once. We choose either to be warriors or to be ordinary men. A second choice does not exist. Not on this earth</quote>
	<quote author="Chang-Tzu">The birth of a man is the birth of his sorrow. The longer he lives, the more stupid he becomes, because his anxiety to avoid unavoidable death becomes more and more acute. What bitterness! He lives for what is always out of reach! His thirst for survival in the future makes him incapable of living in the present</quote>
	<quote author="Winston Churchill">The truth is incontrovertible, malice may attack it, ignorance may deride it, but in the end, there it is</quote>
	<quote author="Winston Churchill">I never worry about action, but only about inaction</quote>
	<quote author="Winston Churchill">Man will occasionally stumble over the truth, but usually manages to pick himself up, walk over or around it, and carry on</quote>
	<quote author="Winston Churchill">Success is not final, failure is not fatal : it is the courage to continue that counts</quote>
	<quote author="Confucius">By three methods we may learn wisdom : first, by reflection, which is the noblest. Second, by imitation, which is the easiest. And third by experience, which is the bitterest</quote>
	<quote author="Confucius">The superior man acts before he speaks, and afterwards speaks according to his action</quote>
	<quote author="Confucius">When it is obvious that the goals cannot be reached, don't adjust the goals, adjust the action steps</quote>
	<quote author="Confucius">To put the world in order, we must first put the nation in order. To put the nation in order, we must put the family in order. To put the family in order, we must cultivate our personal life. And to cultivate our personal life, we must first set our hearts right</quote>
	<quote author="Copernicus">To know that we know what we know, and to know that we do not know what we do not know, that is true knowledge</quote>
	<quote author="Sir William Crookes">We have actually touched the Borderland where Matter and Force seem to merge into one another, the shadowy realm between the Known and Unknown ... I venture to think that the greatest scientific problems of the future will find their solution in this Borderland, and even beyond. Here, it seems to me, lie Ultimate Realities, subtle, far-reaching, wonderful</quote>
	<quote author="Dalai Lama">We can live without religion and meditation, but we cannot survive without human affection</quote>
	<quote author="Dalai Lama">I believe that the very purpose of our life is to seek happiness. That is clear. Whether one believes in religion or not, whether one believes in this religion or that religion, we all are seeking something better in life. So, I think, the very motion of our life is towards happiness</quote>
	<quote author="Leonardo da Vinci">Art is never finished, only abandoned</quote>
	<quote author="Leonardo da Vinci">Where the spirit does not work with the hand there is no art</quote>
	<quote author="Leonardo da Vinci">Why does the eye see a thing more clearly in dreams than the imagination when awake ?</quote>
	<quote author="Democritus of Abdera">Nothing exists except atoms and empty space. Everything else is opinion</quote>
	<quote author="Taisen Deshimaru">Time is not a line, but a series of now points</quote>
	<quote author="Emily Dickinson">The truth dazzles gradually, or else the world would be blind</quote>
	<quote author="Dogen">Cease from practice based on intellectual understanding, pursuing words, and following after speech, and learn the backward step that turns your light inward to illuminate your self. Body and mind of themselves will drop away, and your original face will be manifest</quote>
	<quote author="Freeman Dyson">Mind and intelligence are woven into the fabric of our universe in a way that altogether surpasses our understanding</quote>
	<quote author="Thomas Edison">Many of life's failures are people who did not realize how close they were to success when they gave up</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Matter is Energy. Energy is Light. We are all Light Beings</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Whoever is careless with the truth in small matters cannot be trusted with important matters</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">I have yet to meet a single person from our culture, no matter what his or her educational background, IQ, and specific training, who had powerful transpersonal experiences and continues to subscribe to the materialistic monism of Western science</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">The gift of fantasy has meant more to me than my talent for absorbing knowledge</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Unthinking respect for authority is the greatest enemy of truth</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Few people are capable of expressing with equanimity opinions which differ from the prejudices of their social environment. Most people are even incapable of forming such opinions</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">There are only two ways to live your life. One is as though nothing is a miracle. The other is as though everything is a miracle</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Only a life lived for others is worth living</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Science without religion is lame, religion without science is blind</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">I want to know how God created this world. I am not interested in this or that phenomenon, in the spectrum of this or that element. I want to know His thoughts, the rest are details</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">He who joyfully marches in rank and file has already earned my contempt. He has been given a large brain by mistake, since for him the spinal cord would suffice</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">I am convinced that He (God) does not play dice</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">The most beautiful thing we can experience is the mystical. It is the source of all true art and science</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Imagination is more important than knowledge</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Two things are infinite : the universe and human stupidity... and I'm not sure about the universe</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">A hundred times every day I remind myself that my inner and outer life depend upon the labors of other men, living and dead, and that I must exert myself in order to give in the measure as I have received and am still receiving</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">Do you remember how electrical currents and "unseen waves" were laughed at ? The knowledge about man is still in its infancy</quote>
	<quote author="Albert Einstein">The significant problems we face cannot be solved at the same level of thinking we were at when we created them</quote>
  <quote author="Albert Einstein">Great spirits have always found violent opposition from mediocrities</quote>
	<quote author="T. S. Eliot">We shall not cease from exploration. And the end of all our exploring will be to arrive where we started and know the place for the first time</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">The invariable mark of wisdom is to see the miraculous in the common</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">Truth is beautiful, without doubt. But so are lies</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">What lies behind us and what lies before us are small matters to what lies within us</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">Always do what you are afraid to do</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">God enters by a private door into every individual</quote>
	<quote author="Ralph Waldo Emerson">...the sense of being which in calm hours arises, we know not how, in the soul, is not diverse from things, from space, from light, from time, from man, but one with them and proceeds obviously from the same source.... Here is the fountain of action and of thought.... We lie in the lap of immense intelligence</quote>
	<quote author="Epictetus">There is only one way to happiness and that is to cease worrying about things which are beyond the power of our will</quote>
	<quote author="Epicurus">It is not so much our friends' help that helps us as the confident knowledge that they will help us</quote>
	<quote author="William Faulkner">I believe that man will not merely endure : he will prevail. He is immortal, not because he alone among creatures has an inexhaustible voice, but because he has a soul, a spirit capable of compassion and sacrifice and endurance</quote>
	<quote author="Benjamin Franklin">Democracy must be something more than two wolves and a sheep voting on what to have for dinner</quote>
	<quote author="Galileo Galilei">I do not feel obliged to believe that the same God who has endowed us with sense, reason, and intellect has intended us to forget their use</quote>
	<quote author="Gandhi">We must become the change we want to see</quote>
	<quote author="Gandhi">Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever</quote>
	<quote author="Gandhi">God has no religion</quote>
	<quote author="Gandhi">You may never know what results come of your action, but if you do nothing there will be no result</quote>
	<quote author="Gandhi">When I despair, I remember that all through history the ways of truth and love have always won. There have been tyrants, and murderers, and for a time they can seem invincible, but in the end they always fall. Think of it - always</quote>
	<quote author="Khalil Gibran">Truth is a deep kindness that teaches us to be content in our everyday life and share with the people the same happiness</quote>
	<quote author="Khalil Gibran">Yesterday is but today's memory, tomorrow is today's dream</quote>
	<quote author="Johann Wolfgang von Goethe">Thinking is easy, acting is difficult, and to put one's thoughts into action is the most difficult thing in the world</quote>
	<quote author="Johann Wolfgang von Goethe">Whatever you do, or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius and power and magic in it</quote>
	<quote author="Johann Wolfgang von Goethe">There is nothing more frightful than ignorance in action</quote>
	<quote author="Maxim Gorky">Happiness always looks small while you hold it in your hands, but let it go, and you learn at once how big and precious it is</quote>
	<quote author="J. B. S. Haldane">Reality is not only stranger than we suppose but stranger than we can suppose</quote>
	<quote author="Stephen W. Hawking">To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit</quote>
	<quote author="Stephen W. Hawking">Not only does God play dice, but... he sometimes throws them where they cannot be seen</quote>
	<quote author="Stephen W. Hawking">The whole history of science has been the gradual realization that events do not happen in an arbitrary manner, but that they reflect a certain underlying order, which may or may not be divinely inspired</quote>
	<quote author="Stephen W. Hawking">There are grounds for cautious optimism that we may now be near the end of the search for the ultimate laws of nature</quote>
	<quote author="Napoleon Hill">Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success</quote>
	<quote author="Napoleon Hill">You might well remember that nothing can bring you success but yourself</quote>
	<quote author="Horace">Carpe diem ! Rejoice while you are alive. Enjoy the day. live life to the fullest. Make the most of what you have. It is later than you think</quote>
	<quote author="Victor Hugo">The greatest happiness of life it the conviction that we are loved - loved for ourselves, or rather, loved in spite of ourselves</quote>
	<quote author="Victor Hugo">There is only one thing more powerful than all the armies of the world, that is an idea whose time has come</quote>
	<quote author="William James">The art of being wise is the art of knowing what to overlook</quote>
	<quote author="William James">I believe there is no source of deception in the investigation of nature which can compare with a fixed belief that certain kinds of phenomena are impossible</quote>
	<quote author="William James">We don’t laugh because we’re happy, we’re happy because we laugh</quote>
	<quote author="William James">The greatest discovery of my generation is that a human being can alter his life by altering his attitudes</quote>
	<quote author="James Joyce">A man of genius makes no mistakes. His errors are volitional and are the portals of discovery</quote>
	<quote author="Carl Gustav Jung">Your vision will become clear only when you look into your heart. Who looks outside, dreams. Who looks inside, awakens</quote>
	<quote author="Carl Gustav Jung">As far as we can discern, the sole purpose of existence is to kindle a light in the darkness of being</quote>
	<quote author="Helen Keller">It gives me a deep comforting sense that " things seen are temporal and things unseen are eternal "</quote>
	<quote author="Helen Keller">I can see, and that is why I can be happy, in what you call the dark, but which to me is golden. I can see a God-made world, not a manmade world</quote>
	<quote author="John Maynard Keynes">Words ought to be a little wild, for they are the assaults of thoughts on the unthinking</quote>
	<quote author="Lichtenberg">Perhaps in time the so-called Dark Ages will be thought of as including our own</quote>
	<quote author="Abraham Lincoln">I do not think much of a man who is not wiser today than he was yesterday</quote>
	<quote author="Abraham Lincoln">I have been driven many times to my knees by the overwhelming conviction that I had nowhere to go. My own wisdom, and that of all about me, seemed insufficient for the day</quote>
	<quote author="Martin Luther King">Life's most persistent and urgent question is : What are you doing for others ?</quote>
	<quote author="Martin Luther King">In the End, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends</quote>
	<quote author="Martin Luther King">Darkness cannot drive out darkness. Only light can do that. Hate cannot drive out hate. Only love can do that. Hate multiplies hate, violence multiplies violence, and toughness multiplies toughness, in a descending spiral of destruction. The chain reaction of evil must be broken, or we shall be plunged into the dark abyss of annihilation</quote>
	<quote author="Martin Luther King">Our scientific power has outrun our spiritual power. We have guided missiles and misguided men</quote>
	<quote author="Archibald MacLeish">The dissenter is every human being at those moments of his life when he resigns momentarily from the herd and thinks for himself</quote>
	<quote author="Andre Malraux">Often the difference between a successful person and a failure is not one has better abilities or ideas, but the courage that one has to bet on one's ideas, to take a calculated risk - and to act</quote>
	<quote author="Katherine Mansfield">Risk ! Risk anything ! Care no more for the opinions of others, for those voices. Do the hardest thing on earth for you. Act for yourself. Face the truth</quote>
	<quote author="Marcus Aurelius">To the wise, life is a problem. To the fool, a solution</quote>
	<quote author="Mencius">Friendship is one mind in two bodies</quote>
	<quote author="Edgar Mitchell">Suddenly, from behind the rim of the moon, in long, slow-motion moments of immense majesty, there emerges a sparkling blue and white jewel, a light, delicate, sky-blue sphere laced with slowly swirling veils of white, rising gradually like a small pearl in a thick sea of black mystery. It takes more than a moment to fully realize this is Earth… home. My view of our planet was a glimpse of divinity</quote>
	<quote author="Moliere">It is not only what we do, but also what we do not do, for which we are accountable</quote>
	<quote author="Mother Teresa">God doesn't require us to succeed. He only requires that you try</quote>
	<quote author="R. Nadeau and M. Kafatos">The universe on a very basic level could be a vast web of particles which remain in contact with one another over distance, and in no time</quote>
	<quote author="Friedrich Nietzsche">Art is essentially the affirmation, the blessing, and the deification of existence</quote>
	<quote author="Friedrich Nietzsche">Art is the proper task of life</quote>
	<quote author="George Orwell">Speaking the truth in times of universal deceit is a revolutionary act</quote>
	<quote author="Heinz Pagels">The visible world is the invisible organization of energy</quote>
	<quote author="Marcel Pagnol">The reason people find it so hard to be happy is that they always see the past better than it was, the present worse than it is, and the future less resolved than it will be</quote>
	<quote author="Paracelsus">When a man undertakes to create something, he establishes a new heaven, as it were, and from it the work that he desires to create flows into him... For such is the immensity of man that he is greater than heaven and earth</quote>
	<quote author="Paracelsus">That which the dream shows is the shadow of such wisdom as exists in man, even if during his waking state he may know nothing about it... We do not know it because we are fooling away our time with outward and perishing things, and are asleep in regard to that which is real within ourself</quote>
	<quote author="Pericles">What you leave behind is not what is engraved in stone monuments, but what is woven into the lives of others</quote>
	<quote author="Pablo Picasso">Art is a lie that makes us realize truth</quote>
	<quote author="Max Planck">All matter originates and exists only by virtue of a force… We must assume behind this force the existence of a conscious and intelligent Mind. This Mind is the matrix of all matter</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">Wise men speak because they have something to say. Fools because they have to say something</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">Perhaps there is a pattern set up in the heavens for one who desires to see it, and having seen it, to find one in himself</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">A good decision is based on knowledge and not on numbers</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">A hero is born among a hundred, a wise man is found among a thousand, but an accomplished one might not be found even among a hundred thousand men</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">A state arises, as I conceive, out of the needs of mankind; no one is self-sufficing, but all of us have many wants</quote>	
	<quote author="Plato">Any man may easily do harm, but not every man can do good to another</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">At the touch of love everyone becomes a poet</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">Courage is a kind of salvation</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">Courage is knowing what not to fear</quote>
	<quote author="Plato">For a man to conquer himself is the first and noblest of all victories</quote>
	<quote author="Ramtha">The warrior steps forth to accept the unknown and challenge disbelief, for if it lies in mind it Is, by God !</quote>
	<quote author="Ramtha">If I could take all your words away and give you but a sparse few, they would be: " I now know, I am absolute, I am complete, I am God, I am " If there were no other words but these, you would no longer be limited to this plane</quote>
	<quote author="Ramtha">You cannot see anything that you do not first contemplate as a reality</quote>
	<quote author="Jean-Jacques Rousseau">Quit thy childhood, my friend, and wake up !</quote>
	<quote author="Rumi">Out beyond the ideas of wrongdoing and right-doing, there is a field. I will meet you there</quote>
	<quote author="Rumi">Everything you see has its roots in the unseen world. The forms may change, yet the essence remains the same. Every wonderful sight will vanish. Every sweet word will fade, But do not be disheartened, The source they come from is eternal, growing, branching out, giving new life and new joy. Why do you weep ? The source is within you And this whole world is springing up from it</quote>
	<quote author="George Sand">There is only one happiness in this life : to love and be loved</quote>
	<quote author="Jean-Paul Sartre">Consciousness is a being, the nature of which is to be conscious of the nothingness of its being</quote>
	<quote author="Chief Seattle">Man did not weave the web of life, he is merely a strand in it. Whatever he does to the web, he does to himself</quote>
	<quote author="William Shakespeare">Jesters do oft prove prophets</quote>
	<quote author="George Bernard Shaw">Life isn't about finding yourself. Life is about creating yourself</quote>
	<quote author="George Bernard Shaw">Without art, the crudeness of reality would make the world unbearable</quote>
	<quote author="George Bernard Shaw">The possibilities are numerous once we decide to act and not react</quote>
	<quote author="George Bernard Shaw">All great truths begin as blasphemies</quote>
	<quote author="Socrates">Know thyself</quote>
	<quote author="Swami Sivananda">Do not brood over your past mistakes and failures as this will only fill your mind with grief, regret and depression. Do not repeat them in the future</quote>
	<quote author="St Catherine of Siena">The force that created the unimaginable splendors and the unimaginable horrors has taken refuge in us, and it will follow our commands</quote>
	<quote author="Antoine De Saint-Exupery">How could there be any question of acquiring or possessing, when the one thing needful for a man is to become-to be at last, and to die in the fullness of his being</quote>
	<quote author="Edmund Spenser">We feel and know that we are eternal</quote>
	<quote author="Stendhal">All religions are founded on the fear of the many and the cleverness of the few</quote>
	<quote author="St. Francis of Assisi">There are beautiful and wild forces within us</quote>
	<quote author="St. Francis of Assisi">What we are looking for is what is looking</quote>
	<quote author="Mary Stuart">To be kind to all, to like many and love a few, to be needed and wanted by those we love, is certainly the nearest we can come to happiness</quote>
	<quote author="Russell Targ">Although each of us obviously inhabits a separate physical body, the laboratory data from a hundred years of parapsychology research strongly indicate that there is no separation in consciousness</quote>
	<quote author="Tertullian">The first reaction to truth is hatred</quote>
	<quote author="Henry David Thoreau">Behave so the aroma of your actions may enhance the general sweetness of the atmosphere</quote>
	<quote author="Henry David Thoreau">Go confidently in the direction of your dreams ! Live the life you've imagined. As you simplify your life, the law of the universe will be simpler</quote>
	<quote author="Leo Tolstoy">If you want to be happy, be</quote>
	<quote author="Aart Van Der Leeuw">The mystery of life is not a problem to be solved but a reality to be experienced</quote>
	<quote author="Vincent Van Gogh">I put my heart and my soul into my work, and have lost my mind in the process</quote>
	<quote author="Vincent Van Gogh">I feel that there is nothing more truly artistic than to love people</quote>
	<quote author="Voltaire">Life is thickly sown with thorns, and I know no other remedy than to pass quickly through them. The longer we dwell on our misfortunes, the greater is their power to harm us</quote>
	<quote author="Voltaire">For seventeen hundred years the Christian sect has done nothing but harm</quote>
	<quote author="Ken Wilber">A full-spectrum approach to human consciousness and behavior means that men and women have available to them a spectrum of knowing - a spectrum that includes, at the very least, the eye of flesh, the eye of mind, and the eye of spirit</quote>
	<quote author="Oscar Wilde">Life is too important to be taken seriously</quote>
	<quote author="Oscar Wilde">Women have a wonderful instinct about things. They can discover everything except the obvious</quote>
	<quote author="Oscar Wilde">Keep love in your heart. A life without it is like a sunless garden when the flowers are dead. The consciousness of loving and being loved brings a warmth and richness to life that nothing else can bring</quote>
	<quote author="Oscar Wilde">Life is one fool thing after another whereas love is two fool things after each other</quote>
	<quote author="Marianne Williamson">In the century now dawning, spirituality, visionary consciousness, and the ability to build and mend human relationships will be more important for the fate and safety of this nation than our capacity to forcefully subdue an enemy. Creating the world we want is a much more subtle but more powerful mode of operation than destroying the one we don't want</quote>
	<quote author="R.G. Wolf">Judgment is for fools who defend the shadows in their hearts and minds. People who judge are caught in fear, and do not know who they are...</quote>
	<quote author="Maharishi Mahesh Yogi">Consciousness is the basis of all life and the field of all possibilities. Its nature is to expand and unfold its full potential. The impulse to evolve is thus inherent in the very nature of life</quote>
	<quote author="Maharishi Mahesh Yogi">All speech, action, and behavior are fluctuations of consciousness. All life emerges from, and is sustained in, consciousness. The whole universe is the expression of consciousness. The reality of the universe is one unbounded ocean of consciousness in motion</quote>
	<quote author="Maharishi Mahesh Yogi">All that we are is the result of what we have thought. The mind is everything. What we think, we become</quote>
	<quote author="Maharishi Mahesh Yogi">Knowledge is structured in consciousness. The process of education takes place in the field of consciousness. The prerequisite to complete education is therefore the full development of consciousness - enlightenment. Knowledge is not the basis of enlightenment, enlightenment is the basis of knowledge</quote>
	<quote author="Maharishi Mahesh Yogi">The state of least excitation of consciousness is the field of all possibilities</quote>
	<quote author="Orlando A. Battista">An error doesn't become a mistake until you refuse to correct it</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">All war is deception</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">He who knows when he can fight and when he cannot, will be victorious</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">If ignorant both of your enemy and yourself, you are certain to be in peril</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">Invincibility lies in the defence; the possibility of victory in the attack</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">Opportunities multiply as they are seized</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">The supreme art of war is to subdue the enemy without fighting</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">You have to believe in yourself</quote>
	<quote author="Sun Tzu">Know thy self, know thy enemy. A thousand battles, a thousand victories</quote>
</collection>